Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Albert Carnesale. 1997-1998. UARC.0679
UCLA Library Special Collections
Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Albert Carnesale.
1997-1998
UCLA Library Special Collections
University of California, Los Angeles. Office of the Chancellor
UARC.0679
0.4 Linear Feet
Record Series 679 contains the administrative records of Chancellor Albert Carnesale (1997-2006). Records include congratulatory memorabilia and a Seoul National University scrapbook.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9944751133606533
Biographical note
Albert Carnesale is Chancellor Emeritus and Professor at the University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA). He was Chancellor of the University from July 1, 1997 through June 30, 2006, and now serves as Professor of Public Policy and of Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering.
Scope and Content
Record Series 679 contains the administrative records of Chancellor Albert Carnesale (1997-2006). Records include congratulatory memorabilia and a Seoul National University scrapbook.
This is an active record series; additional University records are expected to be added.
- UC congratulatory plaque for inauguration as Chancellor., 1998. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Westwood Village Community Alliance framed letter of welcome as Chancellor., 1997. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Seoul National University scrapbook for "Association of Pacific Rim Universities.", 1998. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- U31/W6 Instruction - Courses - Experimental & Innovative - Departmental Reviews - Women's Studies., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- U58 Instruction - Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Dance History Program., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- U64 - A - 01 Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Afro-American Studies., 1989-2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- U64 - AM - 02 Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - American Indian Studies., 1986-2001; 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 4 and 5)
- U64/AF - 02 Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - African Area Studies., 2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- U64/ASAM - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Asian American Studies., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- U64/ARCH - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Archaeology., 1999-2006 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- U64/CL - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Comparative Literature., 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- U64 - B - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Biomedical Engineering., 1997-2002 (Box 2, Folder 10 and 11)
- U64 - E - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - European Studies., 2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- U64/FM - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Folklore & Mythology., 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- U64 - H - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Health Economics., 2001-2006 (Box 2, Folder 14 and 15)
- U64-I - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Integrated Manufacturing Engineering., 1995-2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- U64 - I - 01 - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Islamic Studies., 1991-2005 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- U64 - M - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Microbiology & Immunology., 2001-2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- U64 - L - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Latin American Studies., 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- U64 - M - 01 - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Molecular Biology., 2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- U64 - N - 01 - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Neuroscience., 2006 (Box 3, Folder 4 and 5)
- U64/RLL - Instruction - Interdisciplinary Degrees - Departmental Reviews - Romance Linguistics and Literature., 2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- VB4 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - John E. Anderson Graduate School of Management., 1980-1994; 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 7 and 8)
- VD4 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Department of Education., 1972-2002 (Box 3, Folder 9 and 10)
- VD4 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Graduate School of Education - Information Studies., 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- VE4 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Henry Samueli School of Engineering and Applied Science - Departments of Materials, Mechanics & Structures and Energy & Kinetics., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- VE4 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Henry Samueli School of Engineering and Applied Science - Six Year Review of School., 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 13 and 14)
- VE4 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Henry Samueli School of Engineering and Applied Science - Chemical Engineering., 1989-2005 (Box 3, Folder 1989-2005)
- VE4 - 05 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Henry Samueli School of Engineering and Applied Science - Civil Engineering., 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- VE4 - Instructional Unites - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Henry Samueli School of Engineering and Applied Science - Computer Science., 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- VE4-01 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Henry Samueli School of Engineering and Applied Science - Electrical Engineering., 1988-1999 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- VE4 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Henry Samueli School of Engineering and Applied Science - Materials Science & Engineering., 1988-1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- VE4 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Henry Samueli School of Engineering and Applied Science - Mechanical & Aerospace Engineering., 1994-2000 (Box 4, Folder 4 and 5)
- VE4 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Henry Samueli School of Engineering and Applied Science - MS in Online Engineering., 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 2005-2006)
- VF7/A3-01 - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - School of Arts & Architecture - Architecture & Urban Design., 1999-2000; 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 7, 8, and 9)
- VF7/A9 - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - School of Arts & Architecture - Art Department., 1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- VE7/A7 - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - School of Arts and Architecture - Design., 1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- VE7/D3 - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - School of Arts & Architecture - World Arts & Cultures/Dance., 1999 (Box 4, Folder 12 and 13)
- VF7/M8D4E8 - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - School of Arts & Architecture - Ethnomusicology., 1996-2005 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- VH14/D4 - Instructional Units - Degree Programs - Departmental Reviews - School of Dentistry - Oral Biology Program., 2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- VPS4/U7 - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - School of Public Policy & Social Research - Urban Planning., 1995-2005 (Box 5, Folder 1 and 2)
- VH27 - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - Center for Health Sciences - School of Medicine - Human Genetics., 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- VH27/BIOCHEM - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - Center for the Health Sciences - School of Medicine - Biological Chemistry., 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- VH27/BIOM - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - Center for Health Sciences - School of Medicine - Biomathematics., 2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- VH27/NEUROBIO - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - Center for the Health Sciences - School of Medicine - Neurobiology., 2001-2205 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- VH27/PHARM - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - Center for the Health Sciences - School of Medicine - Pharmacology., 2004 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- VH27/RAD-02 - Instructional Units - Center for the Health Sciences - School of Medicine - Radiation Oncology - Biomedical Physics IDP., 1999-2003 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- VH84 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Center for Health Sciences - School of Nursing., 1982-1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- VH84 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - School of Nursing Self Study., 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 10 and 11)
- VH84 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - School of Nursing., 1971-1981 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- VH91-03 - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - Center for Health Sciences - School of Public Health - Environmental Science and Engineering - General Administration and Budget., 1986-2005 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- VH94 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Center for Health Sciences - School of Public Health - Five Year Review of Programs., 1975-1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- VH94 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Center for the Health Sciences - School of Public Health - Six Year Reviews of Programs., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- VH94 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Center for Health Sciences - School of Public Health - Environmental Health Sciences., 1992-2001 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- VH94 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - School of Public Health - Epidemiology., 2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- VH94 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Center for Health Sciences - School of Public Health - Biostatistics., 2004 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- VN/26/BIOL - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Life Sciences - Ecology & Evolutionary Biology - Molecular, Cell and Developmental Biology., 2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- VN26/MIC - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Life Sciences - Microbiology - Microbiology, Immunology & Molecular Genetics (MIMG)., 2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- VN26/PHYSIO - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Life Sciences - Physiological Science., 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- VN26/PSYCH - Instruction Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Life Sciences - Psychology. #1 and 2, 1982-1995; 2003 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- VN36/ATMOS - Instructional Units - Departmental Review and Name Change - College of Letters & Science - Division of Physiological Sciences - Atmospheric and Ocean Sciences., 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- VN36/CHEM - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Physical Sciences - Chemistry and Biochemistry., 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- VN36/EARTH - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews and 8 Year Self-Review - College of Letters & Science - Division of Physical Sciences - Earth and Space Sciences, # 1 and 2., 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 12 and 13)
- VN36/MATH - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Physical Sciences - Mathematics., 2002 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- VN36/PHYCS - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Physical Sciences - Physics and Astronomy., 2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- VN36/STAT - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Physical Science - Statistics., 2002 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- VN46/AERO - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences - Aerospace Studies ROTC., 2003 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- VN46/ECON - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences - Economics., 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- VN46/GEOG - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - Division of Social Sciences - Geography., 2002 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- VN46/HIST - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences - History., 1999-2006 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- VN46/MIL - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Science - Military Science ROTC., 2003 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- VN46/NAV - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences - Naval Science ROTC., 2003 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- VN46/POLISCI - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences - Political Science., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- VN46/SOC - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences - Sociology., 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- VN16/ENGL - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Humanities - English, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- VN16/ENGL-T4 - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Humanities - Teaching English as a Second Language (TESL)/Applied Linguistics - English as a Second Language., 1977-1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- VN16/FR - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Humanities - French., 1983-2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- VN16/GER - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Humanities - Germanic Languages., 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- VN16/ITAL - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Humanities - Italian., 1978-2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- VN16/LING - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Humanities - Linguistics., 1979-2001 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- VN16/MUS - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Humanities - Musicology., 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- VN16/NEL - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Humanities - Near Eastern Languages & Cultures., 1979-2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- VN16/NEL - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Humanities - Near Eastern Languages and Cultures - Islamic Studies., 1977-1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- VN16/PHIL - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Humanities - Philosophy., 1979-2004 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- VN16/SLAV - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Humanities - Slavic Languages and Literatures, #1, 2, and 3., 1979-2005 (Box 7, Folder 11, 12, and 13)
- VN16/SPAN - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Humanities - Spanish and Portuguese., 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- VN16/SPEH - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters & Science - Division of Humanities - Speech - Communication Studies., 1986-2005 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- VN4 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Freshman Cluster Program., 2004 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- VN4 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Afro-American Studies., 1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- VN4 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Latin American Studies., 1980-1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- VN4-02 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - Study of Religion., 1983-2006 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- VN4-03 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - East Asian Studies IDP., 1982-2000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- VN4-08 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - International Development Studies (IDS)., 1993-2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- VN4-09 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - World Arts and Cultures (Formerly Ethnic Arts)., 1978-1986 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- VN4-17 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - Middle Eastern and North African Studies (Formerly Near Eastern Studies)., 1988-2002 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- VN4-15 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - Chemistry/Materials Science IDP., 1999-2006 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- VN4-16 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - Computational & Systemic Biology (Formerly Cybernetics) IDP., 1982-2006 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- VN4-23 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - Southeast Asian Studies IDP., 2001 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- VN4-04 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - Chicano/a Studies Program IDP., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- VN4-C4 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - Cesar E. Chavez Center Interdisciplinary Instruction in Chicano/a Studies., 1997-2002 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- VN4-C4-01 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - Chicano Studies IDP., 1981-1990 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- VN4-H6 - Instructional Units - Instruction and Research Activities - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - Honors Program., 2003 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- VN16 - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - Division of Humanities., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- VN16 - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - Division of Humanities General - South and South East Asian Languages and Cultures., 1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- VN16/Art - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Science and Science - Division of Humanities - Department of Art History., 1991-2004 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- VN16/CLCS - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - Division of Humanities - Department of Classics., 1977-2006 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- VN16/EALC - Instructional Units - Departmental Reviews - College of Letters and Science - Division of Humanities - Department of East Asian Languages and Cultures., 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 20)